<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OSGByte on OSGbyte</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OSGByte on OSGbyte</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://example.com/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/books/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Books are an amazing resource for acquiring knowledge in various fields. Reading the works of pioneers in their respective areas is one of the best ways to grow as a person.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;entrepreneurship&#34;&gt;Entrepreneurship&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Zero to One&lt;/em&gt; (Peter Thiel)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Power Law: Venture Capital and the Making of the New Future&lt;/em&gt; (Sebastian Mallaby)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;human-psychology&#34;&gt;Human Psychology&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Win Friends and Influence People&lt;/em&gt; (Dale Carnegie)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Surrounded by Idiots&lt;/em&gt; (Thomas Erikson)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Power of Positive Thinking&lt;/em&gt; (Norman Vincent Peale)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Psychology of Money&lt;/em&gt; (Morgan Housel)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;productivity&#34;&gt;Productivity&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Atomic Habits&lt;/em&gt; (James Clear)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Deep Work&lt;/em&gt; (Cal Newport)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Never Split the Difference: Negotiating as if Your Life Depended on It&lt;/em&gt; (Chris Voss)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Science of Rapid Skill Acquisition&lt;/em&gt; (PENDING)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;finance&#34;&gt;Finance&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Misssing Billionaires&lt;/em&gt; (Victor Haghani and James White)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The intelligent Investor&lt;/em&gt; (Benjamin Graham) (PENDING)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Advanced Portfolio Management&lt;/em&gt; (Giuseppe Paleologo) (PENDING)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Python for Algorithmic Trading Cookbook&lt;/em&gt; (Jason Strimple) (PENDING)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(PAGE BEING IN CONSTRUCTION)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/quotes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I like quotes, and I&amp;rsquo;m going to post the most beautiful ones to keep track of them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Sometimes it is the people who no one imagines anything of, who do the things that no one can imagine.&amp;rdquo; — &lt;em&gt;Alan Turing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Even in the darkest nights, the sun will always appear.&amp;rdquo; — &lt;em&gt;(Victor Hugo, Les Misérables)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Life is a set of emotions, and we are the result of them.&amp;rdquo; — &lt;em&gt;Myself&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;“When does a man die? When he is hit by a bullet? No! When he suffers a disease? No! When he ate a soup made out of a poisonous mushroom? No! A man dies when he is forgotten!” - (Eiichiro Oda, One Piece)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Best Time To Start Was Yesterday. The Second-Best Time Is Now.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;“The greatest threat to success is not failure but boredom. We get bored with habits because they stop delighting us. The outcome becomes expected. And as our habits become ordinary, we start derailing our progress to seek novelty.” (James Clear)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is talent?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/what-is-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/what-is-talent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-talent&#34;&gt;What is talent?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From time to time, I hear people saying that someone has incredible talent in a particular area, and they feel they can’t compare. Of course, there are individuals with extraordinary abilities—like Magnus Carlsen, Lionel Messi, or top-level athletes. But does that mean you’re talentless? I’ve started to believe this mindset is often an excuse to justify laziness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Malcolm Gladwell, in his book Outliers, discusses the “10,000-hour rule” required to master any skill. This got me thinking: talent might be like the learning rate (alpha) in gradient descent models in machine learning. You might be more or less naturally suited for a particular skill, but ultimately, mastery still demands time and effort. As UFC champion Khabib Nurmagomedov once said, “Hard work beats talent when talent doesn&amp;rsquo;t work hard.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
